duosecurity.com 2018-05-03

# Duo Legal: Privacy | Duo Security

#### Who We Are

Duo Security, Inc. is a company incorporated under the laws of the State of Delaware, USA and whose principal office is located at 123 North Ashley Street, Suite #200, Ann Arbor, Michigan 48104, USA.

In this Privacy Policy when we refer to “Duo Security” or “we”, “us” or “our”, we mean either Duo Security Inc. or the relevant Duo Security group company which provides you with our services and mobile and web-based applications, (including Duo Security UK Limited) as more completely described on our Website (collectively, the “Services”). Duo Security is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit our websites, including, but not limited to [https://www.duo.com](https://www.duo.com/) (collectively, the “Website”) and the customers and users of our services and mobile and web-based applications.

Terms not otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings assigned to them in Duo Security’s Service Terms and Conditions. When you access and use the Services, the Service Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy apply.

If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use personal information, or if you have any other privacy-related questions, please contact us by any of the following means:

By post: Duo Security, Inc., 123 North Ashley Street, Suite #200, Ann Arbor, MI 48104, USA

By facsimile: 1-866-760-4247

By email: privacy@duosecurity.com

#### Introduction

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, share and transfer Personal Information (as defined below) created, inputted, submitted, posted, transmitted, stored or displayed by individuals who interact with and use the Duo Security Website and Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to Personal Information (as defined below) we obtain in our capacity as an employer; employment related data is covered under separate policies and/or notices. This Privacy Policy covers information we collect online, not offline.

Any Personal Information we collect through the Services will be used only in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. When you sign up for or access the Services, including blog updates or newsletters, or when you email us for information, you expressly agree to the use of your information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the use of personal information as described in this Privacy Policy or any changes to it, you should not sign up for, use or access the Services or any features of the Services.

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of this Privacy Policy will govern your use of your Personal Information. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on the Website and update the Privacy Policy modification date. Please check back regularly to review any changes to this Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

#### Personal Information

“Personal Information” is defined slightly differently across the world, but we define “Personal Information” as any information that could be used to identify you or another individual, such as (but not limited to) an individual’s name, email address, or telephone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. Personal Information may include other types of information as well, such as some of the information referred to under the subheadings “Device-Specific Information” and “Service Log Information.”

We also collect non-personal information that does not, on its own, identify any individual person. When non-personal information is combined with other information so that it does identify an individual person, we treat that information as Personal Information.

#### What Information do we Collect?

When you use the Services we may collect, store and process certain information about you, including:

##### Contact Information.

Duo Security may collect, store and process the following contact information in order to provide the Services:

  * **For Organization Users** : If your user profile is created by or at the request of an organization (an “Organization”) of which you are an employee, contractor, member, agent or other participant (each such user referred to as an “Organization User”) your "Organization’s Administrator" may provide us with certain Personal Information, such as your name, email address, and telephone number. We also collect your Organization name and assign you an account name based on your Organization name. Prior to authorizing you to become a user of the Services, your Organization is responsible for notifying you and/or obtaining your consent to the collection of such information, in accordance with applicable laws. Even though your Organization has notified you and/or received your consent to provide us with your Personal Information, when you begin using the Services, you are also providing your consent to the terms in this Privacy Policy and our Service Terms and Conditions.

  * **For Duo Free Users** : If you establish a “Duo Free” account (as compared to an Organization account), and/or if you sign up for our newsletters and email updates we may collect your name, email address, and telephone number.

  * **For Organization Administrators** : for each Organization account we may collect the name, email address, and telephone number of any Organization Administrators, or similar points of contact, within the Organization in order to be able to provide you and the Organization with the Services and to manage your account.

We also collect your email address when you email us for information or sign up for our newsletters and email updates. You can unsubscribe from our newsletters and updates by clicking “Unsubscribe” at the bottom of the newsletter or email update or by emailing mops@duosecurity.com.

**Public Forums** : We collect other information, including Personal Information that you submit to our Website or as you participate in certain interactive features of our Services (such as the publicly accessible blogs or community forums). You should be aware that any information (including Personal Information) you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your Personal Information from our blog or community forum, contact us at privacy@duosecurity.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Testimonials/Reviews/Feedback** : We may post customer testimonials on our Website, which may contain Personal Information. We do obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you want your testimonial removed, please contact us at privacy@duosecurity.com.

**Surveys** : We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys. If you participate, we will request and collect certain Personal Information from you at the time of the survey. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information, such as email or phone number.

When you use the Service we may collect, store and process certain information collected by us from your web browser or from interactions with the Services, including:

**Device-Specific Information** : We also collect device-specific information (e.g. mobile and desktop) from you in order to provide the Services. Device-specific information includes:

  * attributes (e.g. hardware model, operating system, web browser version, as well as unique device identifiers and characteristics (such as, whether your device is “jailbroken,” whether you have a screen lock in place and whether your device has full disk encryption enabled));
  * connection information (e.g. name of your mobile operator or ISP, browser type, language and time zone, and mobile phone number); and
  * device locations (e.g. internet protocol addresses and Wi-Fi).

We may need to associate your device-specific information with your Personal Information on a periodic basis in order to confirm you as a user and to check the security on your device.

**Service Log Information** : When you use the Services, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include which users (by reference to certain Personal Information such as the user’s: username; email address; name; and other information that may be included in open textual fields) are accessing the Services, how users are accessing the Services (including the device-specific information referenced above and type of integration (i.e. application) being protected), the dates and times you are accessing the Services, from where you are accessing the Services (by internet protocol address) and device event information such as crashes, system activity, and hardware settings. We may need to associate this information with other information we collect about you on a periodic basis in order to confirm you as a user and to check the security on your device. We may also do this to improve the Services that we offer you.

**Social Media Widgets** : Our website includes plugins of social media platforms, such as facebook.com of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA; Twitter.com of Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco CA 94107, USA; and google+ of Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, California, 94043, USA. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our websites.

  * You can generally identify the plugins by the respective network’s logo, for instance in combination with a pictogram of a clenched hand with a raised thumb or the addition of a “recommendation”, “like” or “comment.”

Details about purpose and extent of data collection as well as processing and usage of the data by the social media networks can be obtained by reading the privacy policies of [Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php), [Twitter](http://twitter.com/privacy) and [Google](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

#### How do we Use the Information We Collect?

Information we collect may be used for the following purposes:

  * to provide the Services;
  * for billing purposes;
  * to personalize the Services and improve your experience;
  * improving our products, technology and services;
  * for analytical purposes, including use of "Performance Data". Performance Data includes aggregate, de-identified usage information and other aggregate measures of the Services’ performance. We may share aggregated, de-identified Performance Data with third parties to help us better understand our customers’ needs and improve the Services;
  * for marketing and advertising purposes, including sending you promotional email messages about our products and services and registering you for our events. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please opt out here: <https://go.duosecurity.com/UnsubscribePage.html> or send an email to mops@duosecurity.com. For more information about how to change your preferences and to unsubscribe from promotional materials, then please see the section headed “Choice and Consent”. Duo Security does not market or advertise to Organization Users;
  * to prevent, detect, identify, investigate, respond and protect against potential or actual claims, liabilities, prohibited behavior, and criminal activity;
  * to comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, agreements and policies;
  * to perform other activities consistent with this Privacy Policy;
  * to improve the Services and where you have agreed, to provide you updates on how we are improving the Services based on any feedback you might have given; and
  * with respect to Organization Users, to provide you and the Organization with the Services and to manage your account.

#### Data Retention

The time periods for which we retain your Personal Information depend on the purposes for which we use it. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you the Services, unless we are required by law to dispose of it earlier or to keep it longer. We will also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Please contact us as provided in the Notice section below if you have any questions about the information we collect and/or how we use the information we collect.

#### Sharing of Personal Information Collected

Duo Security does not sell, rent, or trade and, except as described in this Privacy Policy, does not share any Personal Information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

Duo Security may transmit or share Personal Information as follows:

  * We may share Personal Information, with our authorized third party vendors, consultants, service providers and hosting partners (currently Amazon Web Services) who perform services for Duo Security (including hardware, software, networking, storage, and other technology and services required to operate, maintain and provide support related to the Services) based on Duo Security’s instructions. These third parties may only use or disclose such Personal Information obtained from Duo Security to perform the Services on Duo Security’s behalf or comply with legal obligations.
  * If you have an Organization account, we may also share Personal Information and/or Device-Specific Information with your Organization and/or your Organization’s third party vendors (with your employer’s consent) in order to operate and maintain the Services. Your device may be subject to your Organization’s policies and practices, which are separate from this Privacy Policy. We have no control over your Organization and your Organization’s third party vendors’ privacy practices, so please read their applicable privacy policies. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to, and Duo Security is not responsible for, use of your Personal Information by these other companies.
  * We may share your Personal Information with third parties to send emails on our behalf, and/or for co-branded and/or co-sponsored marketing and promotional events (such as conference events) offered in conjunction with another company or companies. If you register for or participate in such marketing and promotional events, both Duo Security and such other companies may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded and/or co-sponsored marketing and promotional events. Our Privacy Policy will apply to you with respect to our use of your Personal Information. We have no control over any other companies’ privacy practices, so please read their applicable privacy policies before providing any Personal Information. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to, and Duo Security is not responsible for, use of your Personal Information by these other companies.
  * Duo Security may share information internally with other members of the Duo Security family of companies, including Duo Security UK Limited (a company registered in England and Wales) for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
  * We may also disclose Personal Information; (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process; (ii) to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (iii) as may be required for the purposes of national security; (iv) when we believe disclosure is necessary and appropriate to prevent physical, mental, financial or other harm, injury or loss; or (v) in connection with an investigation of suspect or actual illegal or inappropriate activity or exposure to liability. We may also share such information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Service Terms and Conditions and any other agreements, or as otherwise required by law or to comply with any legal obligation.

When we share Personal Information with a third party, they must contractually agree to comply with privacy and security standards at least as stringent as Duo Security’s when it is handling similar data. When you provide data directly to the third party, the processing is based on their standards (which may or may not be the same as Duo Security’s) and your own independent relationship with that provider.

By accessing, signing up for or using the Services, sending us email, or by signing up for email updates, you provide your express consent to our disclosure of your Personal Information to our third party service providers (such as credit card processors, managed hosting service providers, sub-processors of service data, and technology partners) in order to supply our Services. We do not permit our service providers to use your Personal Information for their own marketing purposes or for any other purpose than in connection with the services they provide to us.

#### Credit Card Information

Some of our customers use credit cards, debit cards or other means to pay for our Services. We do not collect credit card, debit card or personal financial account information through our Website. We use a third party vendor, currently Recurly, Inc., to process our subscription billing. When you provide payment information to pay for the Services, you provide it directly to Recurly, and not to Duo Security. You will automatically be routed to the Recurly website to provide the information Recurly requires to process your transaction. Recurly is a third party vendor and has its own privacy policy, which may be different from this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected by Recurly and Duo Security is not covered by, or responsible for, Recurly’s privacy practices or policy. To learn about Recurly’s privacy practices, please read their privacy policy at <http://recurly.com/legal/privacy>.

#### Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information

You can modify your account information at any time by using the Service administrative interface available at [https://admin.duosecurity.com](https://admin.duosecurity.com/) or by emailing our customer support at support@duosecurity.com. We will respond to your request to access promptly and within no more than 30 days.

#### Cookies and other Tracking Technologies

When you visit our Website or use our Services, we use “cookies” and other tracking technologies like “web beacons” to allow us to remember your user preferences, to maximize the performance of our Website and Services, enhance and personalize your experience and provide marketing communications. They also help ensure that advertisements you see while you are on our Website are more relevant to your interests.

**For further information about cookies and the other tracking technologies we use, along with information about how to disable or block cookies, please see our Cookie Policy at<https://www.duo.com/legal/cookies>**.

#### Security of Information

Duo Security maintains and uses reasonable administrative, organizational, technical and physical safeguards to protect your information from loss, destruction, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure as required by applicable law. These technologies help ensure that your data is safe, secure, and only available to you and to those you provided authorized access (e.g., your users). For example, when you enter confidential information (such as login credentials or information submitted from within the Service), we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). SSL technology is designed to prevent you from inadvertently revealing personal information using an insecure connection. However, no electronic transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so you should take care in deciding what information you send us in this way. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us at privacy@duosecurity.com.

#### Links to Other Sites

Our Website may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Duo Security. Please be aware that Duo Security is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and statements of other sites to understand their information practices. Our Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by our Website and Services.

#### Choice and Consent

We offer certain choices about how we communicate with our users and what Personal Information we obtain from them.

  * You can opt out of receiving promotional emails or text messages from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the email or by emailing mops@duosecurity.com.
  * Many Duo Security products contain settings that allow users or administrators to control how the products collect information. Please refer to the relevant product documentation or contact us through the appropriate technical support channel for assistance.
  * To remove your Personal Information from a Duo Security website testimonial, please contact us at privacy@duosecurity.com.

If you choose to no longer receive marketing information, Duo Security may still communicate with you regarding such things as your security updates, product functionality, responses to service requests, or other transactional, non-marketing/administrative related purposes.

#### Cross-Border Transfer of Your Personal Information

Please be aware that Duo Security may host and process your data and information (including Personal Information), in the United States and other countries through the Duo Security group of companies and third parties that we use to operate and manage the Website and Services, including Amazon Web Services (“AWS”). You may view the AWS privacy policy at <http://aws.amazon.com/privacy>. By signing up for or using the Services, and/or by communicating with us by email, you acknowledge and expressly consent to the transfer and processing of your Personal Information in this way. Any such transfer or processing of your Personal Information will be in accordance with all applicable laws.

#### Your Controls and Choices

You may request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, certain information about the Personal Information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of Personal Information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing as follows:

By post: Duo Security, Inc., 123 North Ashley Street, Suite #200, Ann Arbor, MI 48104, USA

By facsimile: 1-866-760-4247

By email: privacy@duosecurity.com

In addition, we currently do not honor Do Not Track signals.

#### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), as we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. The Website and its content are directed to people who are at least 18 years of age or older.

#### Children

We do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. The Website and its content are directed to people who are at least 18 years of age or older. If you are under the age of 18, you may not use this Website unless you have the consent of, and are supervised by, a parent or guardian.

#### Access to Your Information

You have a right to access, review, change, update or delete your Personal Information at any time by contacting us at privacy@duosecurity.com or by postal mail at Duo Security, Inc., 123 North Ashley Street, Suite #200, Ann Arbor, MI 48104, USA. Please note that we may impose a small fee for access and disclosure of your Personal Information where permitted under applicable law, which will be communicated to you. We do not charge you to update or remove your Personal Information.

#### Contact Us

Duo Security commits to resolving complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Information. If you need to provide a Notice to us under this Privacy Policy or if you have complaints about our compliance with this Privacy Policy, you should first contact us as follows:

By post: Duo Security, Inc., 123 North Ashley Street, Suite #200, Ann Arbor, MI 48104, USA

By facsimile: 1-866-760-4247

By email: privacy@duosecurity.com

#### Business Transactions

Duo Security may assign or transfer this Privacy Policy, and your user account and related information and data, to any person or entity that acquires or is merged with Duo Security.
